

Tomislav Živadinović

zivadinovictomislav@gmail.com

+381648332673

Niš, Serbia

Technologies

Spring Boot

Hibernate

Angular

Thymeleaf

Linux

Git

Swagger

Junit JSP

JavaFX

Languages

Java

MySQL

HTML & CSS

Javascript(ES6)

Education

Software engineering, University of Metropolitan

2019 - Present

High School at Prva niška gimnazija "Stevan Sremac"

Graduated 2019

Summary

My name is Tomislav and I was born on 12th of July 2000. I'm software engineer specializing in the development of web systems. Of all my interests, I would single out backend development, big information systems, and also Linux systems.

Experience

Software Developer at Vega IT

January 2022 - July 2022

Developed variety of application and information systems using most popular technologies. Worked on AEM (adobe experience manager) platform.

Software Developer at Innovative Software

Technologies

August 2020 - January 2022

Intern at Metropolitan University - faculty of Information Technologies involved in development of service-oriented modular information systems using mostly **Angular** and **Spring Boot**. Experience in database design, backup and management mostly **MySQL**. Mostly focused on developing clean backend API's with complex database structure.

Full Stack Developer

Developed a tech blog website using **Thymeleaf** and **Spring Boot** framework. The system has role based authentication and authorization. The system also has complete administration facilities for users, posts, categories etc.

Full Stack Developer

Developed a web application for small family business called **Blinco FF**. Focus of the application is managing with products, employees, customers... Also main focus is creating new invoices and packing lists for exports and printing them.

Technologies used: Spring Boot, Angular, MariaDB

Interests

Cars, mechanics, cycling, skiing, crypto currenices, computer hardware, bushcraft

Portfolio Linkedin Github